Register of the Citizens Committee for Reorganization of the Executive Branch of the Government Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Reports, 1948-1956 (Box 34-43)
  - Issued by various organizations
    - Council of State Governments, "Report on Federal-State Relations,", 1948 July (Folder 43: 2-3)
    - Cresap, McCormick, and Paget Management Engineers, "A Summary of the Hoover Report,", 1950 (Folder 43: 4)
    - Institute of Public Administration, New York City, "The Division of Administrative Management in Federal Bureau of the Budget,", 1948 June (Folder 43: 5)
    - Stanley, Edward and Lawrence Sullivan, "Report on Information Services in the Executive Branch of the Government,", 1948 September (Folder 43: 6)
    - Trundle Engineering Company, "Preliminary Report on Methods and Organization of the Veterans Administration,", 1948 September (Folder 43: 7)
    - West Texas Chamber of Commerce, "Report on West Texas Water Shortage Damages and Application of the Hoover Commission's Domestic Water Recommendations,", 1949 June (Folder 43: 8)
- Congressional Legislation File, 1949-1958 (Box 44-45)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, bills, relating to legislation in the U.S. Congress on issues dealing with the operations of the CCREBG. Arranged alphabetically by subject
  - General
    - General
      - 1949-1952 (Folder 44: 1)
      - (81st Congress), 1950 (Folder 44: 2)
      - (82nd Congress), 1951 (Folder 44: 3)
      - 1956-1957 (Folder 44: 4)
      - (85th Congress), 1957 (Folder 44: 5)
    - Bills
      - General, 1951-1952 (Folder 44: 6)
      - H.R. 8002 (Folder 44: 7-8)
      - Reorganization bills (Folder 44: 9)
    - Recommendations of the President, 1949 October 10 (Box-folder 45: 1)
    - Reports, ("Congressional Canvas Reports), 1957-1958 (Folder 45: 2)
  - Brown, Clarence (Folder 45: 3)
  - Congressional attitudes, 1950 (Folder 45: 4)
  - Taxation (Folder 45: 5)
  - United States. Congress. House of Representatives. Committee on Expenditures in the Executive Departments
    - 1949 September (Folder 45: 6)
    - 1950 June (Folder 45: 7)
  - United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Expenditures in the Executive Departments
    - 1949 September (Folder 45: 8)
    - 1950
      - September (Folder 45: 9)
      - November (Folder 45: 10)
    - 1951 January (Folder 45: 11)
    - 1952 January (Folder 45: 12)
  - Wigglesworth Amendment (Folder 45: 13)
- Reorganization Plans File, 1949-1956 (Box 45-49)
  Reports, memoranda, correspondence, printed matter and other materials relating to the various reorganization plans by the Hoover Commission. Arranged chronologically by year and therein alphabetically by subject
  - 1949
    - General (Folder 45: 14)
    - Congressional hearings (Folder 45: 15)
    - Hoover, Herbert C. Statement on reorganization plans 1-7 before the Senate Committee on Expenditures, June 30 (Box-folder 46: 1)
    - Plans
      - No. 1 (Folder 46: 2)
      - No. 2 (Folder 46: 3)
      - No. 3 (Folder 46: 4)
      - No. 4 (Folder 46: 5)
      - No. 5 (Folder 46: 6)
      - No. 6 (Folder 46: 7)
      - No. 7 (Folder 46: 8)
      - No. 8 (Folder 46: 9)
  - 1950
    - General
      - Correspondence
        - General (Folder 46: 10)
        - Circular letters (Folder 46: 11)
      - Memoranda - United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Expenditures in the Executive Departments staff (Folder 46: 12)
    - Congressional hearings (Folder 46: 13-15)
    - Minority Policy Committee (Folder 46: 16)
    - Plans
      - No. 1 (Folder 46: 17)
      - No. 2 (Folder 46: 18)
      - No. 3 (Folder 46: 19)
      - No. 4 (Folder 46: 20)
      - No. 5 (Folder 46: 21)
      - No. 6 (Folder 46: 22)
      - No. 7 (Folder 46: 23)
      - No. 8 (Folder 46: 24)
      - No. 9 (Folder 46: 25)
      - No. 10 (Folder 46: 26)
      - No. 11 (Folder 46: 27)
      - No. 12 (Folder 46: 28)
      - No. 13 (Folder 46: 29)
      - No. 14 (Folder 46: 30)
      - No. 15 (Folder 46: 31)
      - No. 16 (Folder 46: 32)
      - No. 17 (Folder 46: 33)
      - No. 18 (Folder 46: 34)
      - No. 19 (Box-folder 47: 1)
      - No. 20 (Folder 47: 2)
      - No. 21 (Folder 47: 3)
      - Nos. 22-25 (Folder 47: 4)
      - Nos. 26-27 (Folder 47: 5)
      - No. 27 (Folder 47: 6)
    - United States. President (1945-1953: Truman), Messages from (Folder 47: 7)
    - United States. Congress. Senate - Vote on Plans 1-21, June 10 (Folder 47: 8)
  - 1951
    - General (Folder 47: 9)
    - Plan No. 1 (Folder 47: 10)
    - Suggested reorganization plans (Folder 47: 11)
  - 1952
    - Coates, Charles B., Statement by, June 4 (Folder 47: 12)
    - Congressional hearings (Folder 47: 13-15)
    - McCormick, Robert L., Statements by (Folder 47: 16)
    - Plans (Box 48)
      - No. 1
        - General (Folder 48: 1-3)
        - Press releases (Folder 48: 4)
      - No. 2
        - General (Folder 48: 5-6)
        - Editorials (Folder 48: 7)
        - Form letters (Folder 48: 8)
        - Letter by James C. Auchincloss (Folder 48: 9)
        - Memoranda to Senators (Folder 48: 10)
        - Press releases (Folder 48: 11)
      - Nos. 2-4 (Folder 48: 12)
      - No. 5 (Folder 48: 13)
  - 1953
    - General (Folder 48: 14)
    - Plans
      - No. 1 (Folder 48: 15)
      - No. 2 (Box-folder 49: 1)
      - No. 3 (Folder 49: 2)
      - No. 4 (Folder 49: 3)
      - No. 5 (Folder 49: 4)
      - No. 6 (Folder 49: 5)
      - No. 7 (Folder 49: 6)
      - No. 8 (Folder 49: 7)
      - No. 9 (Folder 49: 8)
      - No. 10 (Folder 49: 9)
  - - Plans, Nos. 1-2, 1954 (Folder 49: 10)
  - - Plans, 1956
    - No. 1 (Folder 49: 11)
    - No. 2 (Folder 49: 12)
- State Committees File, 1954-1956 (Box 49-54)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, and other material generated by the State Committees of the CCREBG. Arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General (Folder 49: 13-14)
  - Correspondence
    - Alabama (Haskell, Preston; Rushton, Allan) (Folder 49: 15)
    - Arizona (Boice, Henry) (Folder 49: 16)
    - Arkansas (Benson, George) (Folder 49: 17)
    - California
      - General (Folder 49: 18)
      - Hancock, Harvey (Box-folder 50: 1)
    - Colorado (Erickson, Roy) (Folder 50: 2)
    - Connecticut (Stacy, Robert) (Folder 50: 3)
    - Delaware (Clark, J. M.; Duffy, William; Gallager, Frank) (Folder 50: 4)
    - Florida (Gay, Clarence; Hume, Frederic) (Folder 50: 5)
    - Georgia (Stickland, Freeman) (Folder 50: 6)
    - Idaho (Holland, A. L.) (Folder 50: 7)
    - Illinois (Stuart, John) (Folder 50: 8)
    - Indiana (Alexander, C. D.) (Folder 50: 9)
    - Iowa (Lawler, Joseph) (Folder 50: 10)
    - Kansas (Murphy, E. P.) (Folder 50: 11)
    - Kentucky (Folder 50: 12)
    - Louisiana (Box-folder 51: 1)
    - Maine (Wyman, William) (Folder 51: 2)
    - Maryland (Radcliffe, George) (Folder 51: 3)
    - Massachusetts (Folder 51: 4)
    - Michigan (Isbey, Frank N.) (Folder 51: 5)
    - Minnesota (Brandt, Ned; Diracles, John) (Folder 51: 6)
    - Mississippi (Sykes, Conwell) (Folder 51: 7)
    - Missouri (Blake, Robert E.) (Folder 51: 8)
    - Montana (MacHaffie, E. D.) (Folder 51: 9)
    - Nebraska (Stuckey, Lyman) (Folder 51: 10)
    - Nevada (Folder 51: 11)
    - New Hampshire (Hill, Herbert W.) (Folder 51: 12)
    - New Jersey (Folder 51: 13)
    - New Mexico (Folder 51: 14)
    - New York (Myrick, Julian S.; Schramm, Henry; Soule, Robert G.) (Folder 51: 15-16)
    - North Carolina (Daniels, G. Neil) (Folder 51: 17)
    - North Dakota (Folder 51: 18)
    - Ohio (Newman, James J.) (Folder 51: 19)
    - Oklahoma (Gordon, Tom P.) (Folder 51: 20)
    - Oregon (Stephenson, C. B.) (Folder 51: 21)
    - Pennsylvania (Folder 51: 22)
    - Region 1 (Connecticut, Maine, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, Rhode Island, Vermont) (Box-folder 52: 1-3)
      - Ely, Joseph B., 1954-1955
      - Sherman, Edward A., 1954-1956
    - Region 2 (Delaware, Maryland, New Jersey, New York, Pennsylvania, West Virginia), Myrick, Julian, 1954-1956 (Folder 52: 4)
    - Region 3 (Florida, Georgia, North Carolina, South Carolina, Virginia), Cooper, Lee E., 1954-1956 (Folder 52: 5)
    - Region 4 (Alabama, Arkansas, Louisiana, Mississippi, Tennessee), Rushton, Allen (Folder 52: 6)
    - Region 5 (Indiana, Kentucky, Michigan, Ohio), Vanderzee, A. (Folder 52: 7)
    - Region 6 (Illinois, Iowa, Missouri, Nebraska, Wisconsin), Stuart, John (Folder 52: 8)
    - Region 7 (Minnesota, North Dakota, South Dakota), Leslie, Frank (Folder 52: 9)
    - Region 8 (Kansas, Oklahoma, Texas), Garrett, P. B. (Folder 52: 10)
    - Region 9 (Southern California), Petree, Neil (Folder 52: 11)
    - Region 10 (Colorado, Utah, Wyoming), Vivian, John (Folder 52: 12)
    - Region 11 (Northern California, Nevada), Blyth, Charles R. (Box-folder 53: 1)
    - Region 12 (Idaho, Montana, Oregon, Washington), Thurston, Severt W. (Folder 53: 2)
    - Rhode Island (Black, Thomas P.) (Folder 53: 3)
    - South Carolina (Edwards, E. M.) (Folder 53: 4)
    - South Dakota (Sexauer, Elmer) (Folder 53: 5)
    - Tennessee (McGovern, E. W.) (Folder 53: 6)
    - Texas (Crow, Trammel) (Folder 53: 7)
    - Utah (Rampton, C. Cash) (Folder 53: 8)
    - Vermont (Hopkins, Carl H.; Davis, Dean C.) (Folder 53: 9)
    - Virginia (Newton, Blake T.) (Folder 53: 10)
    - Washinton (Thurston, Severt W.) (Folder 53: 11)
    - West Virginia (Francis, James D.) (Folder 53: 12)
    - Wisconsin (McKerrow, Gavin) (Folder 53: 13)
    - Wyoming (Josendal, Harold) (Folder 53: 14)
  - Mailings to State Committees
    - 1949 July-December (Folder 53: 15)
    - 1950
      - January-May (Folder 53: 16)
      - June-December (Box-folder 54: 1)
    - 1951
      - January-April (Folder 54: 2)
      - May-June (Folder 54: 3)
      - June-December (Folder 54: 4)
    - 1952
      - January-June (Folder 54: 5)
    - 1956-1958 (Folder 54: 6)
  - Organization chart (Folder 54: 7)
- Subject File, 1948-1958 (Box 54-74)
  Correspondence, memoranda, notes, reports, printed matter and other material. Arranged alphabetically by subject
  - Agriculture
    - General
      - General (Folder 54: 8)
      - Analysis of Agriculture Bill (Folder 54: 9)
      - Congressional hearing transcript (Folder 54: 10)
      - Correspondence
        - General
          - 1951 (Folder 54: 11)
          - 1951-1952 (Box-folder 55: 1)
        - Brannan, Charles, 1952 (Folder 55: 2)
        - Cooley, Harold D., 1952 (Folder 55: 3)
        - McClellan, John, 1951 (Folder 55: 4)
      - Press releases (Folder 55: 5)
      - Rusk statement, 1951 April 7 (Folder 55: 6)
    - Brannan meeting, 1951 August 30 (Folder 55: 7)
    - Senate Bill 1149
      - General (Folder 55: 8)
      - Analysis (Folder 55: 9)
      - Statements by various individuals (Folder 55: 10)
  - Budget and accounting
    - General
      - General (Folder 55: 11-13)
      - General (Box-folder 56: 1-2)
      - Bill drafts (Folder 56: 3)
      - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 56: 4)
      - Congressional reports and reprints (Folder 56: 5)
      - Correspondence (Folder 56: 6)
      - Office memoranda and drafts (Folder 56: 7)
      - Press releases (Folder 56: 8)
      - Statement by McCarthy before the Senate Expenditures Committee, 1950 February 27 (Folder 56: 9)
    - Proposed White Paper No. 2 (Box-folder 57: 1)
    - Public laws (Folder 57: 2)
    - Sponsors (Folder 57: 3)
  - Business enterprises
    - General
      - General (Folder 57: 4-7)
      - Bill drafts, reports (Folder 57: 8)
      - Congressional hearings transcripts (Folder 57: 9)
      - Publications (Box-folder 58: 1)
      - Statement by Robert McCormick, 1958 June 23 (Folder 58: 2)
    - Elimination of Section 633 (Folder 58: 3)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation Act (Folder 58: 4)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (Folder 58: 5)
  - Depot utilization (Folder 58: 6)
  - Education.
    General note
    See Social Security, education, and Indian affairs
  - Federal business enterprises (Folder 58: 7)
  - Federal medical services
    - General (Folder 58: 8)
    - Bill draft (Folder 58: 9)
  - Federal-state relations.
    See Overseas administration, federal-state relations
  - Federal research.
    See Overseas administration, federal-state relations, federal research
  - Food and clothing (Folder 58: 10)
  - Foreign affairs
    - General
      - General (Folder 58: 11)
      - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 58: 12)
      - Correspondence (Folder 58: 13)
      - Press releases (Folder 58: 14)
    - Meck comments on State Department reorganization, 1951 April (Folder 58: 15)
    - Public Law 73 (Folder 58: 16)
  - General management of the Executive Branch of the government
    - General
      - General (Folder 58: 17-19)
      - Agency replies (Box-folder 59: 1)
      - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 59: 2-3)
      - Congressional hearings transcripts (Folder 59: 4)
      - Memorandum on government publications (Folder 59: 5)
      - Press releases (Folder 59: 6)
    - President's Advisory Committee on Management Improvement (Folder 59: 7)
  - General Services Administration
    - General (Folder 59: 8)
    - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 59: 9)
  - Indian affairs.
  - Intelligence activities (Folder 59: 10)
  - Legal services and procedure
    - General (Folder 59: 11-12)
    - General (Box-folder 60: 1-2)
    - Bill drafts (Folder 60: 3)
  - Lending agencies (Folder 60: 4-5)
  - Medical administration and services
    - General
      - General (Folder 60: 6)
      - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 60: 7-8)
      - Congressional hearings transcripts (Box-folder 61: 1)
      - Correspondence (Folder 61: 2)
      - Press releases (Folder 61: 3)
    - National Doctors Committee for Improved Federal Medical Services (Folder 61: 4)
    - President's Commission on Health Needs of the Nation (Folder 61: 5)
  - Military unification
    - General (Folder 61: 6)
    - Bulletins. "Supplements,", Nos. 1-6, 1950 (Folder 61: 7)
    - Clippings (Folder 61: 8)
    - Correspondence (Folder 61: 9)
    - Outline (Box-folder 62: 1)
    - Press releases (Folder 62: 2)
    - Statement by Herbert Hoover before the Armed Services Committee of the House of Representatives, 1949 October 21 (Folder 62: 3)
  - National security
    - General
      - General (Folder 62: 4)
      - Congressional bill drafts (Folder 62: 5)
      - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 62: 6)
      - Correspondence (Folder 62: 7)
      - Statements
        - Eberstadt, Ferdinand, 1949 (Folder 62: 8)
        - Heller, Robert, before the House Armed Services Committee, n.d. (Folder 62: 9)
        - Hoover, Herbert C., 1949 April 13 (Folder 62: 10)
        - Johnson, Robert L., n.d. (Folder 62: 11)
    - Public Laws 36, 216 (Folder 62: 12)
  - Overseas administration, federal-state relations, federal research
    - General (Folder 62: 13-14)
    - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Box-folder 63: 1)
    - Congressional hearings transcripts (Folder 63: 2)
  - Overseas economic operations
    - General (Folder 63: 3)
    - Publications (Folder 63: 4)
  - Paperwork management (Folder 63: 5)
  - Personnel and civil service
    - General (Folder 63: 6)
    - Bill draft (Folder 63: 7)
    - Publications (Folder 63: 8)
  - Personnel management
    - General
      - General
        - 1951 (Folder 63: 9)
        - 1952 (Folder 63: 10)
        - 1953-1955 (Box-folder 64: 1)
      - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 64: 2-3)
      - Congressional hearings transcripts (Folder 64: 4)
      - Correspondence
        - General (Folder 64: 5)
        - Johnson, Robert L.
          - 1950 (Folder 64: 6)
          - 1951 (Folder 64: 7)
        - Mitchell, James P., 1951 (Folder 64: 8)
        - Murray, Tom, 1952 (Folder 64: 9)
      - Press releases (Folder 64: 10-11)
      - Statements
        - Fleming, Arthur, on veterans' preference, n.d. (Folder 64: 12)
        - Johnson, Robert L., before the House Post Office and Civil Service Committee, 1951 February 8 (Folder 64: 13)
        - Watson, James R., before the Senate Civil Service Commission, 1950 March 14 (Folder 64: 14)
    - Congressional hearings (Folder 64: 15)
    - Executive Pay Bill (Box-folder 65: 1)
    - Public laws (Folder 65: 2)
    - Senate Bill 2111 (Folder 65: 3)
    - Special Committee on Personnel Management (Folder 65: 4)
    - Whitten, Congressman (Folder 65: 5)
  - Real property management (Folder 65: 6)
  - Regulatory Commissions (Folder 65: 7)
  - Republican National Convention, 1956 August (Folder 65: 9)
  - Research and development (Folder 65: 10)
  - Social Security, education, and Indian affairs
    - General
      - General (Folder 65: 11)
      - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 65: 12)
      - Correspondence (Folder 65: 13)
      - Press releases (Folder 65: 14)
      - Statement by Herbert Hoover, 1949 June 27 (Folder 65: 15)
    - Public Law 734 (Folder 65: 16)
  - Subversive groups (Folder 65: 17)
  - Surplus property
    - General
      - General (Folder 65: 18)
      - General (Folder 66: 1)
      - Bill draft (Folder 66: 2)
    - Flashlight batteries (Folder 66: 3)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (Folder 66: 4)
  - Transportation
    - General (Folder 66: 5-6)
    - Bill draft (Folder 66: 7)
  - United States. Department of Agriculture
    - General
      - General (Folder 66: 8)
      - Congressional bill drafts and reports (Folder 66: 9)
      - Correspondence (Folder 66: 10)
      - Report to Congress, 1953 December 30 (Folder 66: 11)
    - Agriculture Committee (Folder 66: 12)
    - Agriculture Reorganization Act of 1950 (Folder 66: 13)
    - American Farm Bureau (Folder 66: 14)
  - United States. Department of Commerce
    - General (Folder 66: 15)
    - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 66: 16)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 67: 1)
  - United States. Department of Defense
    - General
      - General (Folder 67: 2-4)
      - Bill draft (Folder 67: 5)
      - Bulletins and press releases (Folder 67: 6)
    - Business organization (Folder 67: 7-9)
    - Business organization (Box-folder 68: 1)
    - House vote on Section 633, Defense Appropriation Act (Folder 68: 2)
  - United States. Department of Labor (Folder 68: 3)
  - United States. Department of the Interior
    - General (Folder 68: 4)
    - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 68: 5)
    - Correspondence (Folder 68: 6)
  - United States. Department of the Treasury (Folder 68: 7)
  - United States. General Services Administration
    - General
      - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 68: 8)
      - Correspondence (Folder 68: 9)
    - Congressional hearings (Folder 68: 10)
    - Public laws (Folder 68: 11)
  - United States. Post Office (Box 69)
    - General
      - General (Folder 69: 1-3)
      - Circular letters (Folder 69: 5)
      - Congressional bills, reports, resolutions (Folder 69: 6-8)
      - Correspondence (Box 70)
        - 1949 (Folder 70: 1)
        - 1950 (Folder 70: 2)
        - 1951-1952 (Folder 70: 3)
      - Press releases (Folder 70: 4-5)
      - Statements
        - Fleming, Arthur, re: HR 8925, 1950 July 1 (Folder 70: 6)
        - Hoover, Herbert C., before the Senate Subcommittee, 1949 June 30 (Folder 70: 7)
        - McCormick, before the House Committee, 1950 June 26 (Folder 70: 8)
    - Advertising Council (Folder 70: 9)
    - Airmail subsidies (Folder 70: 10-12)
    - Airmail subsidies (Box-folder 71: 1-2)
    - Congressional hearings (Folder 71: 3-4)
    - Postal Affairs Task Force (Folder 71: 5)
    - Public laws (Folder 71: 6)
    - Special Committee on Postal Affairs (Folder 71: 7)
    - United States. Congress. Senate. Post Office Committee (Folder 71: 8)
  - Veterans affairs
    - General
      - General (Folder 71: 9)
      - General (Box-folder 72: 1-3)
      - Articles by Victor Cohn, Minneapolis Tribune, 1951 (Folder 72: 4)
      - Congressional bill, reports, resolutions (Folder 72: 5)
      - Congressional hearings transcripts (Box-folder 73: 1)
      - Correspondence (Folder 73: 2-3)
      - Press releases (Folder 73: 4-5)
      - Recommendations of the Hoover Commission (Folder 73: 6)
    - American Legion
      - General (Folder 73: 7)
      - AMVETS (Folder 73: 8)
    - Special Committee on Veterans Affairs (Folder 73: 9)
    - Testimony (Folder 73: 10)
    - "White Paper," No. 1 (Box-folder 74: 1)
  - Water resources and power (Folder 74: 2-5)
- Printed Matter, 1947-1958 (Box 74-92)
  Clippings and publications relating to operations of the CCREBG. Arranged alphabetically by physical form and therein by subject or type of publication, whether issued or collected by the CCREBG
  - Clippings
    - General
      - 1947-1949 (Folder 74: 6)
      - 1948 (Box-folder 75: 1)
      - 1949
        - April-May (Folder 75: 2)
        - May-December (Folder 75: 3)
        - June (Folder 75: 4)
        - July (Folder 75: 5)
        - July (Box-folder 76: 1)
        - August (Folder 76: 2-3)
        - September (Folder 76: 4)
        - October (Folder 76: 5)
        - October (Folder 77: 1)
        - November (Folder 77: 2)
        - December (Folder 77: 3)
        - Various months (Folder 77: 4)
      - 1950
        - January-June (Folder 77: 5)
        - January (Folder 77: 6)
        - February (Box-folder 78: 1-2)
        - March (Folder 78: 3-4)
        - April (Folder 78: 5-6)
        - May (Box-folder 79: 1-2)
        - June (Folder 79: 3)
        - July (Folder 79: 4-5)
        - August-September (Box-folder 80: 1)
        - October-November (Folder 80: 2)
        - November (Folder 80: 3)
        - December (Folder 80: 4-5)
      - 1951
        - January (Folder 80: 6)
        - January (Box-folder 81: 1)
        - February (Folder 81: 2)
        - March (Folder 81: 3)
        - April (Folder 81: 4)
        - May (Folder 81: 5)
        - May (Box-folder 82: 1)
        - June (Folder 82: 2)
        - July (Folder 82: 3)
        - August (Folder 82: 4)
        - September (Folder 82: 5)
        - October (Folder 82: 6)
        - November (Box-folder 83: 1)
        - December (Folder 83: 2)
      - 1952
        - January (Folder 83: 3-5)
        - February (Folder 83: 6)
        - March (Box-folder 84: 1)
        - April (Folder 84: 2)
        - May (Folder 84: 3)
        - June (Folder 84: 4)
      - 1953-1956 (Folder 84: 5)
      - 1955 (Folder 84: 6-7)
      - 1955-1957 (Box-folder 85: 1)
      - 1956 (Folder 85: 2)
      - 1957 (Folder 85: 3-4)
      - 1958 (Folder 85: 5)
    - Agriculture, 1952 (Folder 86: 1)
    - Air Force-Navy investigation, 1949 October (Folder 86: 2)
    - Budget and accounting
      - 1953-1956 (Folder 86: 3)
      - 1957 (Folder 86: 4)
    - Business enterprises, 1953-1956 (Folder 86: 5)
    - Business organization of the Department of Defense, 1953-1956 (Folder 86: 6)
    - California, 1957 (Folder 86: 7)
    - Connecticut, 1957-1958 (Folder 86: 8)
    - Corruption and fraud, 1952 (Folder 86: 9)
    - Depot utilization, 1953-1956 (Folder 86: 10)
    - Federal medical services, 1953-1956 (Box-folder 87: 1)
    - Food and clothing, 1953-1956 (Folder 87: 2)
    - Hoover, Herbert C.
      - 1954-1955 (Folder 87: 3)
      - 1955-1956 (Folder 87: 4)
    - Illinois, 1957 (Folder 87: 5)
    - Inflation, 1957-1958 (Folder 87: 6)
    - Intelligence operations, 1953-1956 (Folder 87: 7)
    - Legal service and procedure, 1953-1956 (Folder 87: 8)
    - Lending agencies, 1953-1956 (Folder 87: 9)
    - Maine, 1957-1958 (Folder 87: 10)
    - Massachusetts (Box 88)
      - 1957 (Folder 88: 1)
      - 1958 (Folder 88: 2)
    - New Hampshire (Folder 88: 3)
    - Overseas economic operations, 1953-1956 (Folder 88: 4)
    - Paperwork, records management (Folder 88: 5)
    - Personnel and civil service, 1953-1956 (Folder 88: 6)
    - Real property management, 1953-1956 (Folder 88: 7)
    - Research and development, 1955-1956 (Folder 88: 8)
    - Rhode Island, 1957-1958 (Folder 88: 9)
    - Surplus property, 1953-1956 (Folder 88: 10)